[{"id": 131, "question": "This girl is almost without shelter. She may not realize it, but she's more exposed to the world than she's ever likely to be again. And it isn't because she's a girl. It could be a boy. It could be you. But why is she 'shelter less ? She s got a place to live in quite a pleasant place by the look of it and if shelter . Doesn't' t mean a house, then what does it mean? When we say someone \"lives a sheltered life\" , we don't only mean that their house is comfortable. We mean that they're protected from too many worries and troubles, that they live in a settled home, probably surrounded by friends and family, and that they don't have to cope with the difficulties the world is full of alone. Certainly no one would say that this girl was leading a sheltered life; she's leaving home to earn her ...\n\nQ: When we say someone \"lives a sheltered life\", we mean they   _   .", "options": ["live in the country", "have a comfortable house", "don t have any worries", "have a secure home life and don t have to face problems alone"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 493, "question": "Warm weather brought by El Nino has had mixed effects on animals in usually snowy places in North America, including New England, according to an Associated Press article. Some animals seem to benefit from having a chance to gather more food before winter, and from expending less energy in daily survival mode. Others, like snowshoe hares, are put at center stage in predators' view when they lack snow for disguising their white fur -- not a good thing for them, of course. Black bears, on the other hand, have been keeping busy gathering nuts and apples, when they would normally have settled into their winter homes by now. Vermont and Massachusetts officials have asked residents to wait till snow falls to take out their bird feeders for the sake of safety, the article said. \"We suggest waitin...\n\nQ: What may upset snowshoe hares because of El Nino?", "options": ["Their being caught more easily.", "Their failing to gather more food.", "Their consuming more energy.", "Their losing sight of their enemies."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 41, "question": "The first time Luca heard the Island of Inventions, he was very young, but the wonders he heard about sounded so unbelievable to him that they were forever kept in his memory. Since then, he never stopped searching clues which might lead him to that place of wonder. He read widely to collect information. Taking a little from here and there, he got quite a clear idea of what the Island was really like. It was a secret place, where all the great men learn and invent together. To be able to join that select club, you had to have created great inventions. Only then could you receive the invitation. To get a chance, Luca spend the years studying and inventing. Every new idea he got, he made it into an invention, and if there were anything he didn't understand, he would seek help. Soon he met ot...\n\nQ: What is the effect of their not being given \"the letter\"?", "options": ["They were disappointed, while it encouraged them to work harder.", "They became desperate and decided to have another way of living.", "They changed their strategy and promote their inventions publicly.", "They gave up their dream while continued their inventions together."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 772, "question": "Attitude is an internal state that influences the choices of personal action made by the individual . Some researchers consider that attitudes come from differences between beliefs and ideas; others believe that attitudes come from emotional states. Here, we focus on the effects of attitudes upon behavior, that is, upon the choices of action made by the individual. The kinds of actions taken by human beings are obviously influenced greatly by attitudes. Whether one listens to classical music or rock, whether one obeys the speed limit while driving, whether one encourages one's husband or wife to express his or her own ideas-all are influenced by attitudes. These internal states are acquired throughout life from situations one is faced with in the home, in the streets, and in the school. Of...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about the learning of attitudes?", "options": ["Attitudes are only learned through one's success.", "Attitudes learned in danger will last no more.", "Copying others' behavior is not a good idea.", "Attitudes can be learned from one's parents."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3059, "question": "Trapped on the 37thFloor Melinda Skaar wasn't expecting any phone calls. Skaar was working late in her office at the First Internet bank of California. By 10:45 that night she was almost ready to go home when the phone rang. Picking it up, she heard a guard shouting. There is a fire! Get out of there. Skaar didn't panic. She figured that it was just a small fire. Her office building was huge. There were 62 floors and her desk was on the 37thfloor. Skaar called out to office mate Stephen Oksas, who also stayed late to work. But when they got out to the hallway, they were met by a cloud of black smoke. Rushing back, Skaar shut the door and filled the space at the bottom of the door with her jacket to keep the smoke out. Then they called 911. before they could call their families, however, th...\n\nQ: what can we conclude from Skaar's action in the fire?", "options": ["she is cleverer than Oksas", "she was trained as a firefighter", "she remained calm in the face of danger", "she had had the experience of being caught in fire."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3199, "question": "Climate change has been blamed for killer hurricanes, sea level rise, and drought, but a new report suggests the effects of climate change might hit the world's coffee supply. Up to 70 percent of the world's coffee supply could be threatened over the next 66 years, according to a new study by researchers at England's Royal Botanic Gardens. Nearly 100 percent of the world's Arabica coffee growing regions could become unsuitable for the plant by 2080, according to the study. Beans from Arabica coffee plants account for about 70 percent of the world's coffee, but the plant also has to be grown under strict weather conditions: they grow well at temperatures between 64 and 70 degrees Celsius, and are highly influenced by frost or temperatures higher than 73 degrees Celsius. With temperatures es...\n\nQ: What does the passage mainly talk about?", "options": ["Climate change affects people in many ways.", "More and more attention has been paid to climate change.", "The world's coffee supply could be threatened by climate change.", "The' growing conditions of Arabica coffee have been improved recently."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1453, "question": "When Caleb Forbes got his first job at an advertising company at the age of 20, he thought he would be at the company for years. But after seven months he was bored. Soon after that, Forbes moved to London. He took four different jobs at three companies over the next five years. Forbes wanted a better job and higher pay---he was never quite satisfied. Welcome to the world of a job hopper. Forbes's story isn't unusual these days and such frequent movement from one job to the next will become more common. The main reason: the nature of employment is changing. There are a lot more contracts and part-time jobs or flexible employment. That leads to people having a greater number of jobs. What's more, layoffs and pay freezes , among other things, have pushed people from one job to another. In so...\n\nQ: Monika Hamori's research showed that   _  .", "options": ["old workers are more likely to move around", "young workers are more likely to be given better jobs", "the less someone moves around, the more he may be paid", "the more someone moves around, the more he may be paid"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2315, "question": "Unemployment in Europe has recently hit record highs. Although Denmark has been protected from economic problems thanks to its low public debt, qualified professionals are still finding it tough to get a job. Danish marketing firm Reputation Copenhagen has come up with a way of helping academics get noticed -- putting them on display in storefront windows. Many highly-trained professionals, ranging from former CEOs to lawyers and tax experts, are currently finding it increasingly difficult to find proper employment on the Danish job market. Some of them have been trying for years, leaving their resumes with dozens of companies, without ever hearing back from them, and are now at a point where they are willing to try anything, even putting themselves in display windows like goods, hoping to...\n\nQ: It can be Inferred that   _  .", "options": ["no companies show interest in the qualified job-seekers in the windows", "both local and international media don't agree with the campaign", "human resource managers have to reply to hundreds of applicants", "to some degree the window displays help people find jobs"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1685, "question": "Americans often say that there are only two things a person can be sure of:death and taxes.Many people feel that the United States has the worst taxes in the world. Taxes are the money that people pay to support their government.There are generally three levels of government in the United States:federal,state,and city;therefore,there are three types of taxes. Salaried people who can earn more than four to five thousand dollars per year must pay a certain part.It depends on their salaries.The federal government has a two-level income tax:that is,15 or 28 percent.$17 850 is the cut off.The tax rate is 15 percent below $17 850 and 28 percent above. The second tax is for the state government:New York,California,or any of the other forty-eight states.Some states have an income tax similar to th...\n\nQ: How much money does an American earning $40 000 per year pay to the federal government as income tax according to the passage?", "options": ["28% of his income.", "15% of his income.", "$17 870.", "$5000."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2762, "question": "When Danny Wallace, 26, got bored, he put an ad on the worldwide web reading simply: \"Join Me. Send a passport photo.\" A year and a half later his east London flat is the headquarters for a global internet-based \"club\" whose members carry out good deeds for strangers every Friday. It's not common for people in London to talk to strangers. If you see someone struggling with something, part of the brain goes \"I want to help\". But the trained part of the brain says: \"They will think you are mad or going to mug them\", so you walk away. Join Me now has about 3,000 members around the world who do an act of kindness every Friday. For example, I'm usually out on a Friday so I go for one of the standard acts -- the unexpected cup of coffee. You might be sitting in a cafe and see an old man in the c...\n\nQ: Which would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Hit-and-run Kindness", "History of Join Me", "Danny Wallace and Join Me", "Why not Join Me"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2525, "question": "TANG Dynasty writer Du Mu once wrote in a poem titled Qingming: \"The ceaseless drizzle drips all the dismal day; So broken-hearted fares the traveler on the way.Where can a wine house be found to drown his sadness ?A cowherd points to Almond Flower (Xing Hua) Village in the distance.\" Qingming, the traditional tomb-sweeping day on the Chinese lunar calendar, falls on April 4 this year. Qingming Jie was proclaimed a Chinese national holiday in 2008. It is a time for remembering loved ones who have departed . People visit their ancestors' graves to sweep away the dirt and get rid of any weeds. They also leave offerings of food and flowers, and burn incense and paper money. Chinese tombs are usually built in the woods or on mountains, far from the city. It is believed that an area that faces ...\n\nQ: All of the following practices are mentioned on tomb-sweeping day EXCEPT  _   .", "options": ["Weeping over the passed-away.", "Flying kites made from bamboo and paper", "Sending flowers to their ancestors' graves.", "Burning incense and paper money for the dead."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2739, "question": "While Americans feel worried about how to look after their children and help them grow, French parents are raising happy, well-behaved children without all the anxiety. Pamela Druckerman, an American mother living in Paris, watched carefully as to why French children seem to behave so much better than American children. Let's listen to what she said. While eating at the restaurants in Paris, I noticed the French kids were either sitting in their chairs waiting for their food or eating fish and even vegetables, happy and satisfied. There was no shouting or crying, and there were no pieces of food around their tables. However, my 2-year-old daughter, Beth, took a brief interest in the food. She even threw food everywhere. She couldn't keep herself in her chair and ran around the table. Thoug...\n\nQ: What is Pamela Druckerman's attitude toward French parents' parenting methods?", "options": ["She doesn't like them", "She considers them helpless", "She thinks they work well.", "She thinks they are hard to follow."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2035, "question": "Many adults in the United States can remember crying the nursery rhyme in the street \"Hot cross buns!\" But only a few people realize this was an early form of advertising. Written advertisements probably began with hieroglyphics more than three thousand years ago, but only a few people could read these symbols. So merchants made signs with pictures or hung their tools over their doors to identify their businesses. In the time of the Roman Empire, wall paintings were a popular form of advertisement. An ad for a play, or some other performance was painted on part of a building or on a wall around a city. People often advertised a house for rent or a freshwater bath in this way, too. Today, large wall signs are still used for outdoor advertising. But outdoor advertising is only a small fracti...\n\nQ: Why did the merchants make signs with pictures or hang their tools over their doors ?", "options": ["To have their houses decorated.", "To make their business known by public.", "To enable people to learn how to read", "To advertise their houses to rent"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3375, "question": "Farmer John and Farmer Bob were neighbors. For more than 30 years, they had been getting along very well. Then their good relationship broke. It began with a small thing, then bitter words, and then weeks of silence. One morning Farmer John woke up to find a stream between the two farms. \"It must be Bob,\" John thought. Then one day there was a knock on John's door. He opened it to find a carpenter standing at the doorway. \"I'm looking for a few days' work,\" the carpenter said. \"I do have a job for you,\" John said. \"Look across the stream at that farm. That's my neighbor Bob. He dug a stream between the two farms. I want you to build a fence--an 8-foot fence. I don't want to see his place or his face any more. I don't have such a neighbor!\" The carpenter said, \"I think I know what to do, si...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["What a Big Fence!", "Farmer and Bridge", "Three Kind Men", "A Fence or a Bridge?"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2304, "question": "Some diaries from Jackie Chan's blog January 4, 2009 Lately I've been busy in Beijing having meetings to discuss my new movie. I also attended John Wu's ceremony of his new movie,Red Cliff,which took two years to complete. I'm good friends with the director John Wu and the main actor Tony Leung. January 5, 2009 Today I went to record a television program for Beijing TV calledVolunteers Across China. This TV program is a large-scale reality show that is based on the idea that \"good people reap good rewards\" and it hopes to encourage people to be more aware and help the \"good people\" who are in difficult situations. January 6, 2009 I'm very pleased to _ that my Jackie Chan automobile website is set up and officially operating! I hope that through this automotive website, I can get in touch w...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the text?", "options": ["It took the author two years to finish the movie Red Cliff.", "People who are in trouble can ask Beijing TV for help.", "Chang Shilei is a famous actor who is good at playing the piano.", "Longwei Xiaozi needs a young actress for a part who can speak English well."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 480, "question": "Friends play an important role in our lives, and although we can't be more familiar with the fact of friendship, we often don't clearly understand how we make friends, especially with Americans. Here are some pieces of advice on making friends with Americans: 1. Visiting places Americans enjoy: parties, churches, restaurants, parks and sports clubs. 2. Be willing to take the first step. Don't wait for them to get close to you. Americans in China may not know you speak English. They may be uncomfortable if they can't speak your language. 3. Use small talks to open the conversation. Ask them where they're from, why they come to China, etc. . Remember: Be careful not to ask personal questions about age, salary and so on. 4. Show an interest in their culture, their country or their job. Americ...\n\nQ: Which is the best way to make friends with an American?", "options": ["To ask him if he is willing to make friends with you.", "To spend a long time learning about him.", "To wait until he tells you his thoughts.", "To ask him to join you for dinner."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3286, "question": "Nigel received a reward for his excellence in study. It began when he was selected to help the teachers in the computer laboratories. The peak of his school career came not when he topped the school but when he was selected for the nationwide competition. Unlike everyone else, Nigel wanted to join the contest because he liked making something out of the Lego sets. Nigel spent the next two months rebuilding the robot. It was during the time that Nigel found out about the prizes for the competition as well as another competitor, Alicia, from a neighboring school. His early intentions were forgotten. Getting the thousand-dollar prize was more important than anything else. Nigel decided to befriend Alicia. Unaware of his intentions, she told him all about the robot that she had been building f...\n\nQ: What is the author's attitude towards Nigel's actions?", "options": ["ambiguous", "defensive", "supportive", "critical"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 633, "question": "When people who are nature lovers worldwide wish all humans to realize the importance of their natural surroundings, many Australians are turning caring for the environment into a way of life. Julie, an Australian housewife in Brisbane is one such example. Even though autumn is approaching Australia's Brisbane in April, one can still watch colorful blooming flowers in Julie's little garden, as she tells that in her community,\"Each of us has a beautiful yard. The whole community, from children to elderly people, takes care of the environment as if they are taking care of their own garden.\" \"Gardening is the most popular club in our community,\" she says. \"A lot of retired people don't just regularly organize gardening lectures, but also personally visit families in the community to provide g...\n\nQ: Why can flowers be seen all year round in Julie's community?", "options": ["Families are taught how to take care of their gardens.", "Gardening lessons are often given by professors.", "The local government provides free gardening training.", "There is enough rainwater to water the flowers regularly."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3077, "question": "One summer day as I was heading to the teaching building I heard someone call my name. I turned around and I saw Philip ,a counselor at our admissions office , standing with another young man, Philip introduced me to him, Stephen, and reminded me that Stephen would be taking one of my classes. Stephen looked at me. With a somewhat painful expression, he asked if my class was going to be hard and if he would be able to pass. I introduced all the things that he would be expected to learn. As we talked, I saw Stephen's eyes getting big with fear. I told him to do all of his assignments, and to hand them in on time. Rather than being overwhelmed by all of the work, I told him the most successful students made a master calendar of all the assignments so they could plan their workload. As the fa...\n\nQ: Compared with other students, Stephen  _  .", "options": ["arranged his workload better.", "failed fewer times than them.", "spent more time on study.", "handed his work earlier."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2526, "question": "TANG Dynasty writer Du Mu once wrote in a poem titled Qingming: \"The ceaseless drizzle drips all the dismal day; So broken-hearted fares the traveler on the way.Where can a wine house be found to drown his sadness ?A cowherd points to Almond Flower (Xing Hua) Village in the distance.\" Qingming, the traditional tomb-sweeping day on the Chinese lunar calendar, falls on April 4 this year. Qingming Jie was proclaimed a Chinese national holiday in 2008. It is a time for remembering loved ones who have departed . People visit their ancestors' graves to sweep away the dirt and get rid of any weeds. They also leave offerings of food and flowers, and burn incense and paper money. Chinese tombs are usually built in the woods or on mountains, far from the city. It is believed that an area that faces ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is correct according to passage?", "options": ["Du Mu ,the well-known poet in Song Dynasty wrote a poem about Qing Ming.", "Qingming Festival used to be a Chinese national holiday.", "People have the custom of flying kites on Qing Ming.", "Those whose ancestors were buried in proper places will have a bright future."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 743, "question": "Lots of people are unhappy with their present weight, but most aren't sure how to change it. You may want to look like the models or actors in magazines and on TV, but those goals might not be healthy or realistic for you. Being healthy is really about being at a weight that is right for you. The best way to find out if you are at a healthy weight or if you need to lose or gain weight is to talk to a doctor or dietitian . If it turns out that you can benefit from weight loss, then you can follow a few of the simple suggestions listed below to get started. _ . Ask your mom or dad to lend help and support and to make lifestyle changes that will benefit the whole family, if possible. Those who have the support of their families tend to have better results with their weight-management programs...\n\nQ: According to the passage, before you decide to lose or gain weight you must know   _  .", "options": ["how you will do it", "how long it should last", "whether you have a healthy weight", "what your realistic goal is"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1159, "question": "Though I have traveled in hundreds of trains, few unusual things have ever happened to me. But one day in a train something did happen. I do not mean that I was hurt: no one was hurt. I do my work in a hot country far away from England. Every September I go there to do my business, and every July I come back to England to have a rest. So every September I go to Paris and take a train from the great French city to Mendova, and at Mendova I catch my ship. There is one very fast train from Paris to Mendova, and it suits me well. It goes as far as Endoran, but it stops at Mendova for a few minutes to let travelers get out or in. It is called The Flying Bluebird. It reaches Mendova at seven minutes past nine in the morning, and it is never late. A ship leaves Mendova at half past eleven, and so...\n\nQ: What do we know about the author and the man sitting next to him?", "options": ["The author didn't like the man's foolish questions", "They talked with each other all night", "They got angry about the window", "The author didn't understand the man's words"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1736, "question": "Throughout July 1945, the Japanese mainland, from Tokyo on Honshu northward to the coast of Hokkaido, were bombed as if an invasion were about to take place. In fact, something far more threatening was at hand, as the Americans were telling Stalin at Potsdam. In 1939 physicists in the United States had learned of experiments in Germany showing the possibility of atomic power and understood the coming damage of an atomic bomb. On August 2, 1939, Albert Einstein warned President Roosevelt of the danger of Nazi Germany's advances in development of the atomic bomb. Eventually, the U.S. Office of Scientific Research Development was created in June 1941 and given combined responsibility with the War Department in the Manhattan Project to develop a nuclear bomb. After four years of research and d...\n\nQ: How many people were killed by the two bombs dropped in Japan?", "options": ["Between 105,000 and 120,000 people.", "Between 35,000 and 40,000 people.", "Between 70,000 and 80,000 people.", "Between 140,000 and 150,000 people."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2641, "question": "In Britain arrangements for inviting and entertaining guests at a wedding are usually the responsibility of the bride's family.In most cases it is mainly friends and relations of both families who are invited but when bride's father is a businessman of some kind, the wedding reception may provide a useful occasion for establishing social connections with clients or customers and other people whose goodwill may be of advantage to him.it is, however, the bride's mother who has the job of sending out the formal printed invitation cards. In the case of a church wedding, the vicar of each parish in which the bride and bridegroom live is normally informed about a month in advance of the ceremony so that an announcement of the coming wedding can be made in church on each of three Sundays before i...\n\nQ: The couple leave for their honeymoon  _  .", "options": ["after the church or register office ceremony", "immediately after the cake has been cut and the speeches made", "at the end of the reception", "as soon as the bride is ready"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1271, "question": "Spring is the time to go out and enjoy the weather and scenery.Here are some events to attend in March of 2012 in Oregon! Oregon Country Fair(OCF), 9 am to 7 pm on March 8 - 10 OCF first started in 1969, and it's blossomed into an outstanding example of what a non - profit should be. OCF is an event of shopping & atmosphere, and food ranging from Indian & Afghani cuisine to Italian & France cuisine.Wonderful craft & music never stop.From the time you get there until the time you leave, everyone has a smile on their faces, and they wave and say hello.For tickets, go and visit www.Oregoncountryfair.org. 30thAnnual Seaside Beach Volleyball Tournament, 8 am to 6 pm on March 12 - 14 The Annual Seaside Beach Volleyball Tournament is an amateur tournament that draws amateur volleyball players to ...\n\nQ: When was the first Seaside Beach Volleyball Tournament held in Oregon?", "options": ["In 1982.", "In 1986.", "In 1988.", "In 1992."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2206, "question": "The picture-like island is rich in scenic beauty. Barbados sightseeing is a photographer's dream that comes true with numbers of natural wonders, breathtaking scenic views, attractive gardens and miles of white, sandy beaches. There's so many things to see and to do, as you check out some of the places of interest on the island. Historical Appeal Experience Full of historical appeal you'll love the impressive collection of beautiful great houses, landmarks, old churches, and traditional ancient houses some of which may date back to the 16th century. Historic Bridgetown, over 375 years old, capital of Barbados, is located with its color1ful fishing boats and splendid yachts ( ) . Check out the Barbados National and see some of the island's most beautiful homes. Nature Charm Enjoyment Nature...\n\nQ: If travelers prefer something risky in Barbados, they may   _  .", "options": ["have a guided island tour", "see the Botanical Garden", "go to Historic Bridgetown", "try a rental drive adventure"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2340, "question": "Whales live in the ocean, but they are not fish. They are warm-blooded mammals and must have air to breathe. The babies are born alive and drink milk from the mother's body. It took millions of years for the whale to develop as it is today. Every spring groups of whales swim hundreds of kilometers to warm places to bear their young. Each group goes to the same place every year. The mothers take very good care of their babies. The fully grown whales are very gentle and playful with each other, and with humans. They \"talk\" to each other with a high noise that sounds beautiful. This\"talking\" can be heard for more than 300 kilometers in open waters. Yet humans kill over a hundred whales a day. They kill them to make whale oils and a lot of other things. Killing them is a modern business with m...\n\nQ: Every spring each group of whales    _   .", "options": ["swim only a few kilometers", "return to the same place as they did before", "go to different places", "go to cold places to bear their young"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1426, "question": "If women are mercilessly exploited year after year, they have only themselves to blame. Because they tremble at the thought of being seen in public in clothes that are out of fashion, they are always taken advantage of by the designers and the big stores. Clothes which have been worn only a few times have to be put aside because of the change of fashion. When you come to think of it, only a woman is capable of standing in front of a wardrobe packed full of clothes and announcing sadly that she has nothing to wear. Changing fashions are nothing more than the intentional creation of waste. Many women spend vast sums of money each year to replace clothes that have hardly been worn. Women who cannot afford to throw away clothing in this way, waste hours of their time altering the dresses they ...\n\nQ: By saying \"the conclusions to be drawn are obvious\", the writer means that   _  .", "options": ["women's inconstancy in their choice of clothing is often laughed at", "women are better able to put up with discomfort", "men are also exploited greatly by fashion designers", "men are more reasonable in the matter of fashion"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1699, "question": "When 15-year-old Louisa Ball takes a nap, she sleeps for days on end, and no amount of shaking can fully wake her up. The British girl has a rare condition called Sleeping Beauty Sickness. Doctors don't know what causes it or how to cure it --only know that it strikes teenagers and goes away by itself after eight to 12 years. Louisa's mum, Lottie, told NBC News that the girl had flulike symptoms just over a year ago. Shortly afterward, she had her first period of long sleeping. She was eventually diagnosed with Kleine-Levin Syndrome, whose victims worldwide may number no more than 1,000. The victims live normally for weeks or months at a time, with normal sleep patterns and normal energy levels. Then, with little warning, they'll go to sleep for days or weeks at a time. So far, Louisa's lo...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["doctors have found the cure for Sleeping Beauty Sickness.", "some people don't believe in the truth of Louisa's symptoms.", "Kleine-Levin Syndrome has no effect on Louisa's study and life.", "the narcolepsy victims sleep longer than those with Kleine-Levin Syndrome."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 595, "question": "In most of the time, I am devoted to my research in the lab with my friend Dave, who loves traveling very much. To make our life colorful and relax ourselves, in July, my friend and I are taking a camping trip. We will travel for four weeks and will tour the United States and part of Canada. We have decided to camp because it does not cost as much as vacationing in hotels. We have to plan very carefully in advance. First, the car we are going to drive is very small, so we have decided to take only one small suitcase each and as few camping things as possible. We will take some medicine with us to prevent insects from hurting us, and also food for picnics. Second, there is a lot to see in the United States and Canada, so we have to decide on the direction we want to drive. The date we are l...\n\nQ: If they are caught in the rain , they will   _  .", "options": ["talk to their families while it rains.", "ask others for help.", "have to stop climbing.", "have to stay in a hotel for the night."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 525, "question": "Runners in a relay race pass a stick in one direction. However, merchants passed silk, gold, fruit, and glass along the Silk Road in more than one direction. They earned their living by traveling the famous Silk Road. The Silk Road was not a simple trading network. It passed through thousands of citied and towns. It started from eastern China, across Central Asia and the Middle East, and ended in the Mediterranean Sea. It was used from about 200 B, C, to about A, D, 1300, when sea travel offered new routes , It was sometimes called the world's longest highway. However, the Silk Road was made up of many routes, not one smooth path. They passed through what are now 18 countries. The routes crossed mountains and deserts and had many dangers of hot sun, deep snow and even battles. Only experie...\n\nQ: New technologies could travel along the Silk Road because people  _  .", "options": ["learned from one another", "shared each other's beliefs", "traded goods along the route", "earned their living by traveling"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 617, "question": "My parents knew their wealth: each other, their six children, and their faith. They tried to live simple lives so that they could have time for what was most important. They didn't busy themselves buying a bigger house, because that would mean working harder to pay the monthly mortgage ,working overtime or taking second job. Who would go running with me then? Who would read stories to me? They didn't burden themselves with buying an expensive car because that would mean worrying about installment bills. Besides, walking to the shopping centre every Saturday afternoon with me gave my dad his needed exercise, and made me feel so special. One of my heart's delights was seeing Dad and Mom in their bedroom at night, after our nightly family prayer. The lights were turned off, and I'd see the fi...\n\nQ: The author believed that his/her parents' happiness was due to(, )", "options": ["their attitude towards life", "their love for each other", "their common interests", "their ability to communicate with each other"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 420, "question": "The day the letter arrived from my university telling me how much I owed them for my first semester, I felt a lump forming in my throat. I hadn't even started my degree and already I was in debt. But although the sum was unsettling, I had peace of mind: I had taken out a loan that would cover the next three years of tuition fees and living expenses. A government body in the UK, the Student Loans Company, provides loans to students whose parents cannot afford to cover the costs themselves. Students forward this amount to the university in advance and agree to repay the loan when they begin their first job. For me, it was a lot of money -around &6,000(60,860 Yuan) per year in total -and much more than I had ever been responsible for. I would receive a couple of thousand pounds per semester -...\n\nQ: The student loan has all of the advantages except that  _  .", "options": ["It can make students live a comfortable life in university.", "It can enable students to carry on with their study.", "It can teach students to spent money wisely.", "It can help to reduce family burden."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1233, "question": "Joan, super visor of the town's morals recently accused George, a local man, of having a drinking problem because she noticed his car outside the town's only bar.She reasoned, it was a logical assumption .George stared at her for a moment and said nothing.Later that evening, he parked his car in front of her house and left it there all night. Why is it that so many of our logical assumptions are just plain wrong? And why do we want to act as if they must be true? In an age long before the Internet, a young American at a party found himself seated next to the famous Chinese diplomat Wellington Koo.Completely not knowing what to say to someone from such a different culture, this young man turned and asked, \"Likee soupee?\" After all, he assumed, don't all Chinese speak in broken English? Mr.K...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we can know George is   _  .", "options": ["clever", "honest", "kind-hearted", "bad-tempered"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 258, "question": "Shopping in the United States changes a lot.About ninety years ago most people shopped in small stores that were owned by one person or a family.Women went from the bakery to the butcher's to the grocer and on to the fruit and vegetable seller in order to get their food for the week. Then about sixty years ago, supermarkets were born.In a supermarket, people could get all the different kinds of food they needed without going to different stores. The next big change in shopping in the United States was the shopping mall.A shopping mall is a group of stores under one roof.Because malls allowed people to shop without worrying about the weather, they soon became very popular.The mall became a place for people to socialize in addition to shopping.If you walk through a mall, you will see older p...\n\nQ: Why can the superstores sell products at much lower prices?", "options": ["Because they are built near small towns.", "Because they are across the United States.", "Because they sell all kinds of products people need.", "Because they can buy goods at a reduction in the price."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1466, "question": "I have only once been in trouble with the law.The whole process of being arrested and taken to court was a rather unpleasant experience at the time, but it makes a good story now. What makes it rather disturbing was the arbitrary circumstances both of my arrest and my subsequent fate in court. It happened in February about twelve years ago.I had left school a couple of months before that and was not due to go to university until the following October.I was still living at home at the time. One morning I was in Richmond, a suburb of London near where I lived.I was looking for a temporary job so that I could save up some money to go traveling.As it was a fine day and I was in no hurry, I was taking my time, looking in shop windows, strolling in the park, and sometimes just stopping and looki...\n\nQ: We can see from the passage that the author   _  .", "options": ["has broken the law only once", "has never broken the law", "has broken the law on more than one occasion", "once broke the law without knowing it"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1092, "question": "What does the word \"home\" mean to you? How do you say the word in French? In Spanish? In your language? Although people usually know what the word means, it often has no exact translation. It's not surprising really, because the idea of home differs from country to country, and from person to person. A home is more than a roof and four walls. It's the cooking, eating, talking, playing and family living that go on inside, which are important as well. And at home you usually feel safe and relaxed. But it's not just that homes look different in different countries, they also contain different things and reveal different attitudes and needs. For example, in cold northern Europe, there's a fire in the living room or kitchen and all the chairs face it. In the south, where the sun shines a lot an...\n\nQ: You can   _   at home according to the passage.", "options": ["eat, play, and teach students", "cook, talk, and play games", "swim, eat, and make friends", "do nothing"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 749, "question": "We do not know when man first began to use salt, but we do know that it has been used in many different ways throughout history. Historical evidence shows, for example, that people who lived over 3,000 years ago ate salted fish. Thousands of years ago in Egypt, salt was used to preserve the dead. Stealing salt was considered a major crime during some periods of history. In the eighteenth century, for example, if a person was caught stealing salt, he could be put in prison and his ears could be cut off. In the Roman Empire, one of the most important roads was the one that carried salt from the salt mines to Rome. Guards were stationed along the route to protect against salt thieves, and they received their pay in salt, thus bringing the English word, salary. Any guard who fell asleep while ...\n\nQ: The expression \"not worth his salt\" used today refers to the one who   _  .", "options": ["fails to do his work well", "should not be paid in salt", "doesn't want to work at all", "should use less salt"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3162, "question": "One night recently , I was driving down a two-lane highway at about 60 miles an hour . A car approached from the opposite direction at about the same speed . As we passed each other , I caught the other driver's eye for only a second . I wondered whether he might be thinking , as I was , how dependent we were on each other at that moment . I was relying on him not to fall asleep , not to be put off by a phone conversation, not to cross over into my lane and bring my life to a sudden end . Though we had never spoken a word to each other , he relied on me in just the same way . Multiplied a million times over, I believe that is the way the world works . At some level , we all depend upon one another . Sometimes that dependence requires us simply not to do something like crossing over the dou...\n\nQ: The author said that they depended on each other in the same way because  _  .", "options": ["the approaching car was very dangerous", "they both drove their car at a terrific speed", "he might be killed out of the other's careless driving", "it was dark and the road was not wide enough"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2133, "question": "Bruce Jun Fan Lee was born in the hour of the Dragon, between 6 and 8 a.m., in the \"Year of the Dragon\" on November 27, 1940 at the Jackson Street Hospital in San Francisco's Chinatown. Today, a plaque in the hospital's entry remembers the place of his birth. Bruce's birth, in the hour and the year of Dragon, is a powerful symbol in Chinese astrology . It would be a strong indication of the powerful life that was to be lived by Bruce Lee and the explosive influence his life would have on countless others. At the age of three months, Lee Hoi Chuen, his wife Grace and baby Bruce returned to Hong Kong where Bruce would be raised until the age of 18. Probably because of the long ocean voyage and the change in climates, Bruce was not a strong child in his very early years, a condition that woul...\n\nQ: Learning kung fu diligently from Master Yip Man, Bruce soon realized that   _  .", "options": ["one can't master kung fu skills without much practice", "only through physical combat can one defend his honor", "one can never defeat himself unless trained by a master", "excellent kung fu skills can strengthen one's confidence considerably"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3475, "question": "When his book Little Princes begins, Conor Grennan is planning a year-long trip around the globe, a journey that began with a three-month volunteer service at the Little Princes Children's home, an orphanage in Nepal. When he arrived at the orphanage, Conor was immediately welcomed by all the children even though he had no previous experience in working with children. He quickly grew to love the job. But it wasn't long before Conor came to learn that the children were not orphans at all -- they were actually children who had been separated from their parents by a child trafficker . This realization turned Conor's global journey into a strong desire to try to find a way to reunite these children with their families. As a part of his efforts, Conor did a great amount of work when he was back...\n\nQ: It can be learned from the passage that Conor Grennan   _  .", "options": ["is the author of Little Princes", "is determined to remain single", "likes teaching very much", "is a friend of the author's"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 883, "question": "If you're in charge of a project, the key to success is getting everyone to want to help you. As a director, I point, I suggest, I gently push the actors in the direction I want them to go. In the 1986 movie Nothing in Common, Jackie Gleason's character, Max Basner, gets fired (or unemployed) from his job as a clothing salesman. The scene, shot on a boat, shows Max's despair about being out of work. I was looking for some gesture that would allow Max to show his feelings. Jackie had far more experience at everything than I did, and at first I was frightened (very much afraid). What could I possibly tell \"The Great One\" about acting? Out of fear I decided to direct by suggestion, and I sat down with Gleason to talk about the scene. \"So Max is sad, right?\" I said. Gleason nodded. \"And he's p...\n\nQ: The most suitable (or proper) title for the passage is   _  .", "options": ["Directing a Film", "The Key to Success", "A Wonderful Experience", "Working with Film Stars"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2358, "question": "The crowd cheered and cheered. The man with the horn waved and smiled his great smile. \"More! More!\" cried the crowd. And Louis Armstrong took his horn and began to play again. Here he was in England. Now a famous man, he was rich. He knew many important people. Wherever he went, people knew his name. They wanted to hear his music. As he played the sad, slow songs, Louis thought of his home in New Orleans. He lived there as a boy. It was a busy, exciting city. But Louis's family was very poor. He went to work to help his mother. He also went to school. One of Louis's teachers asked him to join the school band. \"This horn is yours until you leave our school,\" his teacher said. Louis's music was jazz and he loved it. He remembered all the music he heard. He didn't learn to read music until h...\n\nQ: Louis was very smart but he didn't learn to read music until   _  .", "options": ["he left school.", "he was in the school band.", "he became famous.", "he became a grown-up."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2468, "question": "We human beings haven't been good friends to animals. For thousands of years, we have been polluting the environment, making it hard for animals to live on the planet. We have been killing animals for their fur, feathers or meat, or simply because they are dangerous. As a result, many kinds of animals have disappeared forever. Hundreds more are on the endangered list today. Should we care about animals? Of course we should. If animals of a certain kind all disappear, they will never come back again. Animals are more than just resources of things we need. Every kind of animal has its place in the balance of nature. Destroying any kind of animal can lead to many problems. For example, when farmers killed large numbers of hawks, the corn and grain that the farmers stored were destroyed by rat...\n\nQ: Why do people kill animals?", "options": ["Animals cause many serious problems.", "They kill animals for something they need.", "Animals destroy their natural resources.", "They kill animals to protect the environment"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 871, "question": "To Whom It May Concern: prefix = st1 /Chengdu #7 High School is proud to send an Odyssey of the MindTeam to World Competition this year. They competed inShanghaifor the National Competition and were selected to go to World. The World Competition will be held at the University of Maryland in theUnited Statesat the end of May. Odyssey of the Mind is a creative problem-solving competition. Teams of up to seven students will solve a complex problem using innovative ideas and materials. They will be judged on originality in three separate categories. Odyssey of the Mind competitions emphasize team work and creative \"out of the box\" solutions. The strength of this program is that the solutions are the work of the students only - neither coaches nor parents are allowed input. During the competiti...\n\nQ: After reading this passage, a manager in a promising hi-tech company would  _  .", "options": ["leave it alone", "think it funny", "perhaps start his own Odyssey of the Mindteam", "probably be likely to offer a bit of help"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2833, "question": "Almost everyone suffers from a headache sometimes.But some people suffer from repeated, frequent headaches. What is headache? What causes it? What can be done about a headache? What research is being done on headaches? The dictionary defines headache simply as \"a pain in the head.\" What most people mean by headache is a pain which lasts several minutes or hours.It covers the whole head, or one side of it, or perhaps the front or the back of the head.To add to the confusion about a definition, some people call tight feeling in the head a headache. A headache is important because it can be the first warning of a serious condition which probably could be controlled if discovered early.If a person removes the warning, day after day, with a pain-killer, he may pass the point of easy control. Th...\n\nQ: Which is true according to the passage?", "options": ["Headache has no effect on others.", "Headache may cover the whole body.", "Headache may last several minutes or hours.", "Headache is just the tight feeling in the head."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1079, "question": "What did you dream about last night? Did your teeth fall out or did you fly? Maybe you died or someone you know did.Or maybe you were back in high school.These are among the most common dreams people have and they all mean something.Here are some of the most common dreams and their interpretations or symbolism. Dreams of flying.Dreams of flying represent feelings of freedom that may result from an instance when you overcome a limitation or obstacle.Usually, children have more flying dreams than adults, because children are more open to their possibilities, and adults have often accepted limitations imposed by society. Teeth falling out.Food in a dream is symbolic of knowledge because food nourishes the physical body and knowledge nourishes the soul.Teeth are a means to break down food or k...\n\nQ: The woman' s dream is mentioned mainly to   _  .", "options": ["tell us nothing but an interesting story", "show us what a nightmare is like", "tell us that women are always changeable", "show us the way to deal with a recurring dream"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1791, "question": "It's wonderful to go to another country, complete a volunteer project and feel that you really have a positive influence. But how can you become an international volunteer? * Plan practically. Contact the organization a few months before leaving and find out if there are materials which are rare and hard to attain for the project. What you often consider plentiful here, such as nails or hammers, is in great need in other parts of the world. * Do the project together, not on your own. You are a guest in the community. The most successful result is not that you build something and walk away, but that you and the community build something as a team. Share skills and build together. * Be flexible. Not everything is going to happen as planned. Often the other country doesn't have the right tool...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["What prepares you to become a volunteer.", "Where volunteers are needed most in the world.", "Why volunteering is popular with young people.", "How volunteers develop a relationship with local people."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2640, "question": "In Britain arrangements for inviting and entertaining guests at a wedding are usually the responsibility of the bride's family.In most cases it is mainly friends and relations of both families who are invited but when bride's father is a businessman of some kind, the wedding reception may provide a useful occasion for establishing social connections with clients or customers and other people whose goodwill may be of advantage to him.it is, however, the bride's mother who has the job of sending out the formal printed invitation cards. In the case of a church wedding, the vicar of each parish in which the bride and bridegroom live is normally informed about a month in advance of the ceremony so that an announcement of the coming wedding can be made in church on each of three Sundays before i...\n\nQ: The reception normally takes place in the bride's home if  _  .", "options": ["this is a large one.", "there is enough room to entertain the people invited.", "the parents cannot afford to hire a hall.", "there is to be no party afterwards."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3244, "question": "Dr. Paul Kelly, head of Monkeseaton Community High School in North Tyneside, said it would mean the end of sleeping in lessons before lunch, after experiments showed teenagers could have different body clocks from adults and younger children. Russell Foster, an Oxford professor of neuroscience , tested the memory of 200 Monkseaton pupils at 9 am and 2 pm using pairs of words, and discovered a 9% improvement in the afternoon. Students correctly identified 51% of word pairs in the latest session, compared with 42% in the morning. Tayler McCullough, 15, one of the test subjects, said the majority of students would welcome the extra hours in bed, \"I'm extremely hard to get up in the morning. One or two people like to get to school early, but most of us would be up for going in later. I'm sure ...\n\nQ: Foster's opinion on teenagers' getting up late is that   _  .", "options": ["teenagers are practical", "teenagers are lazy-bones", "it's based on their body development", "it's good for their learning and health"], "answer": 2}]